<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Advanced Documentation on Project X</title><link>https://xtls.github.io/en/documents/level-2/</link><description>Recent content in Advanced Documentation on Project X</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>cn</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xtls.github.io/en/documents/level-2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Getting Started with Transparent Proxy</title><link>https://xtls.github.io/en/documents/level-2/transparent_proxy/transparent_proxy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xtls.github.io/en/documents/level-2/transparent_proxy/transparent_proxy/</guid><description>What is Transparent Proxy(TProxy)? General speaking the Transparent Proxy is not let the device which has been proxied feeling itself to be proxied, further speaking is the proxied device do not need to run any proxy software(such as Xray, V2rayNG and so on). When you connected to the network, your device has been proxied.
And it means that, the proxy software is running in other places, such as running in the router, all the devices connected to the Internet via the router can automatically be proxied.</description></item><item><title>TProxy Configuration</title><link>https://xtls.github.io/en/documents/level-2/tproxy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xtls.github.io/en/documents/level-2/tproxy/</guid><description>This configuration is based on New V2Ray vernacular tutorial on TProxy (transparent proxy) , adding the new features of Xray, using the VLESS + XTLS Splice solution, and change the default outbound proxy distribution method to the default outbound direct connection in the old tutorial, the user should modify it according to the actual situation.
All the configurations in this article have been successfully tested in Raspberry Pi 2B and Ubuntu 20.</description></item><item><title>Transparent proxy to circumvent Xray traffic via gid</title><link>https://xtls.github.io/en/documents/level-2/iptables_gid/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xtls.github.io/en/documents/level-2/iptables_gid/</guid><description>In the existing transparent proxy configuration(New V2Ray vernacular tutorial on transparent proxy 、 New V2Ray vernacular tutorial on transparent proxy (TProxy) 、 Transparent proxy（TProxy）configuration tutorial)tutorials, the circumvention of Xray traffic is achieved by using mark. That is, mark the Xray outbound traffic and circumvent the Xray traffic by setting up iptables rules for direct connection of the traffic corresponding to the mark to prevent loopback.
There are several problems with this method:</description></item></channel></rss>